{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260591100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260591100"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 4da16818-932d-4a8d-9595-7dcf4e36f395"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-8-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260597140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260597140"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 4da16818-932d-4a8d-9595-7dcf4e36f395"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260603644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260603643"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 4da16818-932d-4a8d-9595-7dcf4e36f395"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260609870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260609870"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 4da16818-932d-4a8d-9595-7dcf4e36f395"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260623968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260623967"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260632491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260632491"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" START_ASALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260637327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260637326"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" START_ASALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260638924","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260638924"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260640512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260640512"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260644623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260644623"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260646185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260646185"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260652019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260652019"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260653697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260653697"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260656673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260656672"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260656839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260656839"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260676496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260676495"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 58bf24e9-2d24-4985-88e8-65b3cbbe44e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260676574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260676574"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" d80314cf-400d-4956-b573-de38d88b4c43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260688788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260688788"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260689174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260689174"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260689662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260689662"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260690012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260690011"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260690422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260690422"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260690901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260690900"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260691131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260691131"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260694408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260694407"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260694449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260694449"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260695178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260695177"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260695581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260695581"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260695881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260695880"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260696091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260696090"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260696288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260696288"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260696619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260696618"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260696853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260696853"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260700048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260700047"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260700451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260700450"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260703030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260703030"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260703233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260703233"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260703437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260703437"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260706866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260706866"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260710582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260710582"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260711610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260711610"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260714365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260714365"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260714747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260714747"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260715235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260715235"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260715583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260715583"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260715989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260715989"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260716467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260716467"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260716691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260716691"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260719951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260719950"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260719993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260719993"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260720717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260720717"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260721115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260721114"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260721413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260721413"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260721622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260721622"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260721821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260721821"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260722137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260722137"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260722361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260722361"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260725037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260725034"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260725140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260725140"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192249"," gameId":" 26a4387c-8878-4e77-99b9-6b797481235c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}